{
    "id": "384f28bdfe26464a99219379af0b9f71",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She wears ……………………… make-up for my taste.",
            "description": "Too much shows undesirable extremes. It is used before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "too much",
                "too many",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We got ……………………….. answers to our advertisement.",
            "description": "We use too many before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "too much",
                "too many",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I arrived ………………………. early.",
            "description": "Before adverbs, we use too, not too much.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………. generous.",
            "description": "Before an adjective without a noun, we use too.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is too …………………………. to go out.",
            "description": "We can use too before adjective + a/an + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "a cold day",
                "cold a day",
                "cold day"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The water is …………………………. salty for us to drink.",
            "description": "We cannot use too much before an adjective without a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. children love animals.",
            "description": "When most means the majority of, it is used without the.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t eat ………………………….. breakfast.",
            "description": "We use much before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "much of",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t see ………………………… a city in a day.",
            "description": "We use much of before a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "much of",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. the people here seem to know each other.",
            "description": "We use most of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… Indians can understand Hindi.",
            "description": "We use most before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "The most of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………………….. you are there?",
            "description": "We use many of before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of",
                "much of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}